[
    {
        "question": "For to us a child is born, to us a son is given; and the government shall be upon(1) his shoulder, and his name shall be called(2) Wonderful Counselor, Mighty God, Everlasting Father, Prince of Peace. Footnotes (1) 9:6 Or *is upon* (2) 9:6 Or *is called* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 9:6",
        "rank": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "Therefore the Lord himself will give you a sign. Behold, the virgin shall conceive and bear a son, and shall call his name Immanuel.(1) Footnotes (1) 7:14 *Immanuel* means *God is with us* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 7:14",
        "rank": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Spirit of the Lord GOD is upon me, because the LORD has anointed me to bring good news to the poor;(1) he has sent me to bind up the brokenhearted, to proclaim liberty to the captives, and the opening of the prison to those who are bound;(2) Footnotes (1) 61:1 Or *afflicted* (2) 61:1 Or *the opening* [of the eyes] *to those who are blind*; Septuagint *and recovery of sight to the blind* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 61:1",
        "rank": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "but they who wait for the LORD shall renew their strength; they shall mount up with wings like eagles; they shall run and not be weary; they shall walk and not faint. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 40:31",
        "rank": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "But he was pierced for our transgressions; he was crushed for our iniquities; upon him was the chastisement that brought us peace, and with his wounds we are healed. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 53:5",
        "rank": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cHow you are fallen from heaven, O Day Star, son of Dawn! How you are cut down to the ground, you who laid the nations low! (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 14:12",
        "rank": "258"
    },
    {
        "question": "Surely he has borne our griefs and carried our sorrows; yet we esteemed him stricken, smitten by God, and afflicted. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 53:4",
        "rank": "304"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the year that King Uzziah died I saw the Lord sitting upon a throne, high and lifted up; and the train(1) of his robe filled the temple. Footnotes (1) 6:1 Or *hem* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 6:1",
        "rank": "329"
    },
    {
        "question": "We have all become like one who is unclean, and all our righteous deeds are like a polluted garment. We all fade like a leaf, and our iniquities, like the wind, take us away. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 64:6",
        "rank": "435"
    },
    {
        "question": "All we like sheep have gone astray; we have turned\u2014every one\u2014to his own way; and the LORD has laid on him the iniquity of us all. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 53:6",
        "rank": "470"
    },
    {
        "question": "For my thoughts are not your thoughts, neither are your ways my ways, declares the LORD. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 55:8",
        "rank": "480"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cListen to me, you who pursue righteousness, you who seek the LORD: look to the rock from which you were hewn, and to the quarry from which you were dug. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 51:1",
        "rank": "489"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cCome now, let us reason(1) together, says the LORD: though your sins are like scarlet, they shall be as white as snow; though they are red like crimson, they shall become like wool. Footnotes (1) 1:18 Or *dispute* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 1:18",
        "rank": "520"
    },
    {
        "question": "The ox knows its owner, and the donkey its master\u2019s crib, but Israel does not know, my people do not understand.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 1:3",
        "rank": "536"
    },
    {
        "question": "A voice cries:(1) \u201cIn the wilderness prepare the way of the LORD; make straight in the desert a highway for our God. Footnotes (1) 40:3 Or *A voice of one crying* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 40:3",
        "rank": "563"
    },
    {
        "question": "My people\u2014infants are their oppressors, and women rule over them. O my people, your guides mislead you and they have swallowed up(1) the course of your paths. Footnotes (1) 3:12 Or *they have confused* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 3:12",
        "rank": "570"
    },
    {
        "question": "There shall come forth a shoot from the stump of Jesse, and a branch from his roots shall bear fruit. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 11:1",
        "rank": "605"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cYou are my witnesses,\u201d declares the LORD, \u201cand my servant whom I have chosen, that you may know and believe me and understand that I am he. Before me no god was formed, nor shall there be any after me. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 43:10",
        "rank": "613"
    },
    {
        "question": "fear not, for I am with you; be not dismayed, for I am your God; I will strengthen you, I will help you, I will uphold you with my righteous right hand. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 41:10",
        "rank": "636"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cCome, everyone who thirsts, come to the waters; and he who has no money, come, buy and eat! Come, buy wine and milk without money and without price. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 55:1",
        "rank": "642"
    },
    {
        "question": "You keep him in perfect peace whose mind is stayed on you, because he trusts in you. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 26:3",
        "rank": "715"
    },
    {
        "question": "but your iniquities have made a separation between you and your God, and your sins have hidden his face from you so that he does not hear. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 59:2",
        "rank": "776"
    },
    {
        "question": "Behold my servant, whom I uphold, my chosen, in whom my soul delights; I have put my Spirit upon him; he will bring forth justice to the nations. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 42:1",
        "rank": "888"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cThe bricks have fallen, but we will build with dressed stones; the sycamores have been cut down, but we will put cedars in their place.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 9:10",
        "rank": "911"
    },
    {
        "question": "so shall my word be that goes out from my mouth; it shall not return to me empty, but it shall accomplish that which I purpose, and shall succeed in the thing for which I sent it. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 55:11",
        "rank": "921"
    },
    {
        "question": "The wolf shall dwell with the lamb, and the leopard shall lie down with the young goat, and the calf and the lion and the fattened calf together; and a little child shall lead them. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 11:6",
        "rank": "1,027"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cSeek the LORD while he may be found; call upon him while he is near; (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 55:6",
        "rank": "1,048"
    },
    {
        "question": "Thus says the LORD, your Redeemer, the Holy One of Israel: \u201cI am the LORD your God, who teaches you to profit, who leads you in the way you should go. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 48:17",
        "rank": "1,065"
    },
    {
        "question": "Comfort, comfort my people, says your God. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 40:1",
        "rank": "1,066"
    },
    {
        "question": "Let me sing for my beloved my love song concerning his vineyard: My beloved had a vineyard on a very fertile hill. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 5:1",
        "rank": "1,067"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cFor behold, I create new heavens and a new earth, and the former things shall not be remembered or come into mind. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 65:17",
        "rank": "1,084"
    },
    {
        "question": "And he touched my mouth and said: \u201cBehold, this has touched your lips; your guilt is taken away, and your sin atoned for.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 6:7",
        "rank": "1,093"
    },
    {
        "question": "But now thus says the LORD, he who created you, O Jacob, he who formed you, O Israel: \u201cFear not, for I have redeemed you; I have called you by name, you are mine. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 43:1",
        "rank": "1,110"
    },
    {
        "question": "Behold, the LORD\u2019s hand is not shortened, that it cannot save, or his ear dull, that it cannot hear; (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 59:1",
        "rank": "1,121"
    },
    {
        "question": "Thus says the LORD, the King of Israel and his Redeemer, the LORD of hosts: \u201cI am the first and I am the last; besides me there is no god. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 44:6",
        "rank": "1,122"
    },
    {
        "question": "He was despised and rejected(1) by men, a man of sorrows(2) and acquainted with(3) grief;(4) and as one from whom men hide their faces(5) he was despised, and we esteemed him not. Footnotes (1) 53:3 Or *forsaken* (2) 53:3 Or *pains*; also verse 4 (3) 53:3 Or *and knowing* (4) 53:3 Or *sickness*; also verse 4 (5) 53:3 Or *as one who hides his face from us* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 53:3",
        "rank": "1,132"
    },
    {
        "question": "It shall come to pass in the latter days that the mountain of the house of the LORD shall be established as the highest of the mountains, and shall be lifted up above the hills; and all the nations shall flow to it, (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 2:2",
        "rank": "1,147"
    },
    {
        "question": "Have you not known? Have you not heard? The LORD is the everlasting God, the Creator of the ends of the earth. He does not faint or grow weary; his understanding is unsearchable. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 40:28",
        "rank": "1,232"
    },
    {
        "question": "From the sole of the foot even to the head, there is no soundness in it, but bruises and sores and raw wounds; they are not pressed out or bound up or softened with oil. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 1:6",
        "rank": "1,233"
    },
    {
        "question": "Arise, shine, for your light has come, and the glory of the LORD has risen upon you. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 60:1",
        "rank": "1,245"
    },
    {
        "question": "All you beasts of the field, come to devour\u2014 all you beasts in the forest. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 56:9",
        "rank": "1,268"
    },
    {
        "question": "The grass withers, the flower fades, but the word of our God will stand forever. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 40:8",
        "rank": "1,269"
    },
    {
        "question": "He shall judge between the nations, and shall decide disputes for many peoples; and they shall beat their swords into plowshares, and their spears into pruning hooks; nation shall not lift up sword against nation, neither shall they learn war anymore. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 2:4",
        "rank": "1,287"
    },
    {
        "question": "And I heard the voice of the Lord saying, \u201cWhom shall I send, and who will go for us?\u201d Then I said, \u201cHere I am! Send me.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 6:8",
        "rank": "1,313"
    },
    {
        "question": "And the daughter of Zion is left like a booth in a vineyard, like a lodge in a cucumber field, like a besieged city. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 1:8",
        "rank": "1,327"
    },
    {
        "question": "Behold, my servant shall act wisely;(1) he shall be high and lifted up, and shall be exalted. Footnotes (1) 52:13 Or *shall prosper* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 52:13",
        "rank": "1,350"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cIs not this the fast that I choose: to loose the bonds of wickedness, to undo the straps of the yoke, to let the oppressed(1) go free, and to break every yoke? Footnotes (1) 58:6 Or *bruised* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 58:6",
        "rank": "1,362"
    },
    {
        "question": "But the LORD raises the adversaries of Rezin against him, and stirs up his enemies. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 9:11",
        "rank": "1,373"
    },
    {
        "question": "To the teaching and to the testimony! If they will not speak according to this word, it is because they have no dawn. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 8:20",
        "rank": "1,442"
    },
    {
        "question": "Woe to those who call evil good and good evil, who put darkness for light and light for darkness, who put bitter for sweet and sweet for bitter! (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 5:20",
        "rank": "1,443"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who has believed what he has heard from us?(1) And to whom has the arm of the LORD been revealed? Footnotes (1) 53:1 Or *Who has believed what we have heard?* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 53:1",
        "rank": "1,476"
    },
    {
        "question": "How beautiful upon the mountains are the feet of him who brings good news, who publishes peace, who brings good news of happiness, who publishes salvation, who says to Zion, \u201cYour God reigns.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 52:7",
        "rank": "1,580"
    },
    {
        "question": "He was oppressed, and he was afflicted, yet he opened not his mouth; like a lamb that is led to the slaughter, and like a sheep that before its shearers is silent, so he opened not his mouth. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 53:7",
        "rank": "1,637"
    },
    {
        "question": "I form light and create darkness; I make well-being and create calamity; I am the LORD, who does all these things. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 45:7",
        "rank": "1,661"
    },
    {
        "question": "It is he who sits above the circle of the earth, and its inhabitants are like grasshoppers; who stretches out the heavens like a curtain, and spreads them like a tent to dwell in; (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 40:22",
        "rank": "1,673"
    },
    {
        "question": "And one called to another and said: \u201cHoly, holy, holy is the LORD of hosts; the whole earth is full of his glory!\u201d(1) Footnotes (1) 6:3 Or *may his glory fill the whole earth* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 6:3",
        "rank": "1,703"
    },
    {
        "question": "Your country lies desolate; your cities are burned with fire; in your very presence foreigners devour your land; it is desolate, as overthrown by foreigners. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 1:7",
        "rank": "1,723"
    },
    {
        "question": "I will make it a waste; it shall not be pruned or hoed, and briers and thorns shall grow up; I will also command the clouds that they rain no rain upon it. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 5:6",
        "rank": "1,805"
    },
    {
        "question": "For the head of Syria is Damascus, and the head of Damascus is Rezin. And within sixty-five years Ephraim will be shattered from being a people. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 7:8",
        "rank": "1,824"
    },
    {
        "question": "Yet it was the will of the LORD to crush him; he has put him to grief;(1) when his soul makes(2) an offering for guilt, he shall see his offspring; he shall prolong his days; the will of the LORD shall prosper in his hand. Footnotes (1) 53:10 Or *he has made him sick* (2) 53:10 Or *when you make his soul* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 53:10",
        "rank": "1,857"
    },
    {
        "question": "Remember the former things, those of long ago; I am God, and there is no other; I am God, and there is none like me.",
        "answer": "Isaiah 46:9",
        "rank": "1,858"
    },
    {
        "question": "As the rain and the snow come down from heaven, and do not return to it without watering the earth and making it bud and flourish, so that it yields seed for the sower and bread for the eater",
        "answer": "Isaiah 55:10",
        "rank": "1,871"
    },
    {
        "question": "Unless the LORD Almighty had left us some survivors, we would have become like Sodom, we would have been like Gomorrah.",
        "answer": "Isaiah 1:9",
        "rank": "1,902"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Lord says: \"These people come near to me with their mouth and honor me with their lips, but their hearts are far from me. Their worship of me is based on merely human rules they have been taught.\"",
        "answer": "Isaiah 29:13",
        "rank": "1,922"
    },
    {
        "question": "When you pass through the waters, I will be with you; and when you pass through the rivers, they will not sweep over you. When you walk through the fire, you will not be burned; the flames will not set you ablaze.",
        "answer": "Isaiah 43:2",
        "rank": "2,001"
    },
    {
        "question": "For this is what the LORD says \u2013  he who created the heavens, he is God; he who fashioned and made the earth, he founded it; he did not create it to be empty, but formed it to be inhabited \u2013  he says: \"I am the LORD, and there is no other.\"",
        "answer": "Isaiah 45:18",
        "rank": "2,037"
    },
    {
        "question": "Therefore I will give him a portion among the great, and he will divide the spoils with the strong, because he poured out his life unto death, and was numbered with the transgressors. For he bore the sin of many, and made intercession for the transgressors.",
        "answer": "Isaiah 53:12",
        "rank": "2,070"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Sovereign LORD has given me an instructed tongue, to know the word that sustains the weary. He wakens me morning by morning, wakens my ear to listen like one being taught.",
        "answer": "Isaiah 50:4",
        "rank": "2,104"
    },
    {
        "question": "Nevertheless, there will be no more gloom for those who were in distress. In the past he humbled the land of Zebulun and the land of Naphtali, but in the future he will honor Galilee of the nations, by the Way of the Sea, beyond the Jordan \u2013",
        "answer": "Isaiah 9:1",
        "rank": "2,105"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"If you keep your feet from breaking the Sabbath and from doing as you please on my holy day, if you call the Sabbath a delight and the LORD's holy day honorable, and if you honor it by not going your own way and not doing as you please or speaking idle words,\"",
        "answer": "Isaiah 58:13",
        "rank": "2,168"
    },
    {
        "question": "For this is what the high and exalted One says \u2013  he who lives forever, whose name is holy: \"I live in a high and holy place, but also with those who are contrite and lowly in spirit, to revive the spirit of the lowly and to revive the heart of the contrite.\"",
        "answer": "Isaiah 57:15",
        "rank": "2,197"
    },
    {
        "question": "Look in the scroll of the LORD and read: None of these will be missing, not one will lack her mate. For it is his mouth that has given the order, and his Spirit will gather them together.",
        "answer": "Isaiah 34:16",
        "rank": "2,198"
    },
    {
        "question": "When you come to appear before me, who has asked this of you, this trampling of my courts?",
        "answer": "Isaiah 1:12",
        "rank": "2,212"
    },
    {
        "question": "But you are brought down to the realm of the dead, to the depths of the pit.",
        "answer": "Isaiah 14:15",
        "rank": "2,259"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"I am the LORD; that is my name! I will not yield my glory to another or my praise to idols.\"",
        "answer": "Isaiah 42:8",
        "rank": "2,283"
    },
    {
        "question": "I am the LORD, and there is no other; apart from me there is no God. I will strengthen you, though you have not acknowledged me",
        "answer": "Isaiah 45:5",
        "rank": "2,327"
    },
    {
        "question": "And the Spirit of the LORD shall rest upon him, the Spirit of wisdom and understanding, the Spirit of counsel and might, the Spirit of knowledge and the fear of the LORD. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 11:2",
        "rank": "2,328"
    },
    {
        "question": "He will tend his flock like a shepherd; he will gather the lambs in his arms; he will carry them in his bosom, and gently lead those that are with young. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 40:11",
        "rank": "2,386"
    },
    {
        "question": "For the LORD is our judge; the LORD is our lawgiver; the LORD is our king; he will save us. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 33:22",
        "rank": "2,387"
    },
    {
        "question": "therefore thus says the Lord GOD, \u201cBehold, I am the one who has laid(1) as a foundation in Zion, a stone, a tested stone, a precious cornerstone, of a sure foundation: \u2018Whoever believes will not be in haste.\u2019 Footnotes (1) 28:16 Dead Sea Scroll *I am laying* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 28:16",
        "rank": "2,414"
    },
    {
        "question": "no weapon that is fashioned against you shall succeed, and you shall refute every tongue that rises against you in judgment. This is the heritage of the servants of the LORD and their vindication(1) from me, declares the LORD.\u201d Footnotes (1) 54:17 Or *righteousness* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 54:17",
        "rank": "2,434"
    },
    {
        "question": "Thus says the LORD: \u201cHeaven is my throne, and the earth is my footstool; what is the house that you would build for me, and what is the place of my rest? (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 66:1",
        "rank": "2,464"
    },
    {
        "question": "Be broken,(1) you peoples, and be shattered;(2) give ear, all you far countries; strap on your armor and be shattered; strap on your armor and be shattered. Footnotes (1) 8:9 Or *Be evil* (2) 8:9 Or *dismayed* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 8:9",
        "rank": "2,465"
    },
    {
        "question": "Bring no more vain offerings; incense is an abomination to me. New moon and Sabbath and the calling of convocations\u2014 I cannot endure iniquity and solemn assembly. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 1:13",
        "rank": "2,466"
    },
    {
        "question": "And I said: \u201cWoe is me! For I am lost; for I am a man of unclean lips, and I dwell in the midst of a people of unclean lips; for my eyes have seen the King, the LORD of hosts!\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 6:5",
        "rank": "2,495"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cCry aloud; do not hold back; lift up your voice like a trumpet; declare to my people their transgression, to the house of Jacob their sins. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 58:1",
        "rank": "2,524"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cRemember not the former things, nor consider the things of old. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 43:18",
        "rank": "2,525"
    },
    {
        "question": "(1) The people who walked in darkness have seen a great light; those who dwelt in a land of deep darkness, on them has light shone. Footnotes (1) 9:2 Ch 9:1 in Hebrew (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 9:2",
        "rank": "2,559"
    },
    {
        "question": "these I will bring to my holy mountain, and make them joyful in my house of prayer; their burnt offerings and their sacrifices will be accepted on my altar; for my house shall be called a house of prayer for all peoples.\u201d (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 56:7",
        "rank": "2,598"
    },
    {
        "question": "The vision of Isaiah the son of Amoz, which he saw concerning Judah and Jerusalem in the days of Uzziah, Jotham, Ahaz, and Hezekiah, kings of Judah. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 1:1",
        "rank": "2,599"
    },
    {
        "question": "I will greatly rejoice in the LORD; my soul shall exult in my God, for he has clothed me with the garments of salvation; he has covered me with the robe of righteousness, as a bridegroom decks himself like a priest with a beautiful headdress, and as a bride adorns herself with her jewels. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 61:10",
        "rank": "2,632"
    },
    {
        "question": "Thus says the LORD, your Redeemer, who formed you from the womb: \u201cI am the LORD, who made all things, who alone stretched out the heavens, who spread out the earth by myself, (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 44:24",
        "rank": "2,689"
    },
    {
        "question": "And he said, \u201cGo, and say to this people: \u201c\u2018Keep on hearing,(1) but do not understand; keep on seeing,(2) but do not perceive.\u2019 Footnotes (1) 6:9 Or *Hear indeed* (2) 6:9 Or *see indeed* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 6:9",
        "rank": "2,725"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cI, I am he who blots out your transgressions for my own sake, and I will not remember your sins. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 43:25",
        "rank": "2,760"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cTurn to me and be saved, all the ends of the earth! For I am God, and there is no other. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 45:22",
        "rank": "2,794"
    },
    {
        "question": "let the wicked forsake his way, and the unrighteous man his thoughts; let him return to the LORD, that he may have compassion on him, and to our God, for he will abundantly pardon. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 55:7",
        "rank": "2,827"
    },
    {
        "question": "Listen to me, O coastlands, and give attention, you peoples from afar. The LORD called me from the womb, from the body of my mother he named my name. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 49:1",
        "rank": "2,828"
    },
    {
        "question": "\u201cBehold, God is my salvation; I will trust, and will not be afraid; for the LORD GOD(1) is my strength and my song, and he has become my salvation.\u201d Footnotes (1) 12:2 Hebrew *for Yah, the Lord* (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 12:2",
        "rank": "2,903"
    },
    {
        "question": "They shall not hurt or destroy in all my holy mountain; for the earth shall be full of the knowledge of the LORD as the waters cover the sea. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 11:9",
        "rank": "2,904"
    },
    {
        "question": "Your new moons and your appointed feasts my soul hates; they have become a burden to me; I am weary of bearing them. (ESV)",
        "answer": "Isaiah 1:14",
        "rank": "2,905"
    }
]